http://www.abphotos.com/index.php?view=privacy

My Cart
FACEBOOK
Welcome to Andrew Brooks Photography, LLC
HomeAbout AndrewClients
MS & HS CHRISTMAS FINE ARTS PROGRAMFPD Band Concert 10/20/2020Middle School Girls Basketball vs MDS 12/5/2020Boys Middle School Basketball vs SEA 12/03/2020Middle School Girls vs SEA 12/03/20Varsity Girls Basketball vs Central Macon 11/23/20Middle School Swimming Action from 11/16/2020Varsity Swimming action pictures from 11/12/2020Senior & Mom together that I took after Pep rallyPep Rally group pictures FPD Pep Rally 11/13/2020 Mom's and Seniors dancing at the Pep Rally 11/13/2020 Seniors dancing at the Pep Rally 11/13/2020Mom's dancing at the Pep Rally 11/13/2020Herndon Cox Wedding FPD Band vs ACE 9/5/20Newborn and KidsHigh School SeniorsFamily Portraits Sport Action http://abphotos.com/wordpress/macon/
Photo Restoration
Contact us
MENU
MENU
My Cart
Clients
MS & HS CHRISTMAS FINE ARTS PROGRAM
FPD Band Concert 10/20/2020
FPD Band vs ACE 9/5/20
Photo Restoration Contact usHomeAbout AndrewNewborn and KidsHigh School SeniorsFamily Portraits Sport Action
http://abphotos.com/wordpress/macon/
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how ABPhotos uses and protects any information that you give ABPhotos when you use this website.
ABPhotos is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name
contact information including email address & mailing address
demographic information such as postcode and preferences
IP address & browser data
other information relevant to order processing and/or offers
What we do with the information we gather
We collect information about you to process your orders, manage your account and, if you agree, send you offers related to our products & services.
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your system hard drive. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs and remember information about your preferences.
These cookies are necessary to provide you with services available through our website and to use some of its features, such as access to secure areas. However, these identifiers do not store any personal data.
Below are the cookies that may be used from our website.
PHPSESSID
Random value to start sessions
ms_session
A unique random identifier for user experience and actions such as saving contents of your shopping cart.
persid
An encrypted ID to automatically log you into your account if you choose the remember me option when creating an account or logging in.
vid
A visitor ID number used for our statistical system.
lv
The date of your last visit for our statistical system.
emview
Set if you have viewed our mailing list popup offer (value of 1). Required so it does not show to you each time you visit our site.
hasloggedin
Set if you have previously logged into your account (value of 1)
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to our social accounts and/or other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement.
Controlling your personal information
When using parts of our website you may encounter forms to fill out with your email address or other personal information at which time you will have the option whether we may contact your pertaining to that form or event.
If you have created an account with us, you can update your account information at any time by logged into your account and using the My Account area.
If you wish to have your information removed from our system, you may email us at abphotos176@gmail.com with your request and we will process that as soon as possible.
Sign up for email promotions.
Your information is safe with us and won't be shared.
no thanks
Thank you for signing up!
Close
ABPhotos
Home   About Andrew   Clients   Newborn and Kids   High School Seniors   Family Portraits
Sport Action
http://abphotos.com/wordpress/macon/  Photo Restoration
Contact us
©2020 All Rights Reserved.
Content may not be used without prior express written consent.
Built with Sytist
By continuing to browse or by clicking Accept Cookies, you agree to the storing of cookies on your device necessary to provide you with the services available through our website.
Accept   Privacy & Cookie Policy
Loading More Photos
Scroll To Top
Close | Clear All & Close
Close Window
Loading
Close
